revisionmaths.com 2015-12-28

# Privacy | content, privacy | Revision Maths

**Privacy Policy**

**Effective 25** **th** **August 2015**

**About RevisionMaths.com**

RevisionMaths.com (formerly MathsRevision.net) is an online service that allows our members to revise from educational materials. Revision Maths is owned by Revision World Networks Ltd. Many functions of Revision Maths are shared directly with [RevisionWorld.com](http://www.revisionworld.com/) for these areas please refer to the Revision World [Privacy Policy](http://www.revisionworld.com/content/privacy).

RevisionMaths.com cares deeply about online privacy If you have any questions concerning this privacy policy, please [contact us](http://www.revisionworld.com/contact).

**Use of Cookies**

RevisionMaths.com uses cookies to store visitors' preferences and to record session information, for purposes including ensuring that visitors are not repeatedly offered the same advertisements and to customize newsletter, advertising, and Web page content based on browser type and user profile information. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. You may be able to configure your browser to accept or reject all or some cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set -- each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences -- however, you must enable cookies from RevisionMaths.com in order to use most functions on the site Please note that RevisionMaths allows 3rd party advertisers that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Advertisers' use of cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not the RevisionMaths Privacy Policy.

**Links**

RevisionMaths.com contains links to sites. RevisionMaths.com is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When linking to another site a user should read the privacy policy stated on that site. Our privacy policy only governs information collected on RevisionMaths.com.

**Third Party Advertising**

Ads appearing on this Web site may be delivered to users by RevisionMaths.com or one of our Web advertising partners. Our Web advertising partners may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement. In this way, ad servers may compile information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw their advertisements and determine which ads are clicked on. This information allows an ad network to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by RevisionMaths.com and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Changes in Our Privacy Policy**

From time to time we may make changes to our privacy policy If we make changes, we will post them on our site to make users aware of what the changes are so users will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and when we may disclose it. A User is bound by any minor changes to the policy when she or he uses the site after those changes have been posted If, however, we are going to use users' personally identifiable information in a manner materially different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify by posting a notice on our Web site for 30 days.
